Weiss (Barbizon), Benjamin Photographs 5967 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Benjamin Weiss (Barbizon) Photographs
1959-1969
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Weiss, Benjamin
5967 P
1.67 cubic feet
1.7 linear ft.
Photographs.
Collection of Barbizon photographs (1958-1969), cartoons from the 1950's, and several photo albums of miscellaneous photographs.
7984593
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 24, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Scope and Contents
Collection of Barbizon photographs (1958-1969), cartoons from the 1950's, and several photo albums of miscellaneous photographs.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5206-D: Local 1199 Drug Division Records 5588: David L. Cole Papers 5619/012: ACTWU Company Files 5733: Peter Seitz Arbitration Files 5780 P: ILGWU Photographs 5780 P N45: ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs 5780/083: ILGWU Sol Chaikin Papers 5780/084: ILGWU Wilbur Daniels Papers 5780/088: ILGWU Gus Tyler Papers 5780/102 P: ILGWU Justice Photographs 5780/113: ILGWU Wilbur Daniels Papers 5780/115: ILGWU Western States Region Records 5780/144: ILGWU Organizing Department Records 5780/146: ILGWU Master Agreements, Out-of-Business Contracts 5780/147: ILGWU Independents, Out-of-Business Contracts 5780/152: ILGWU David Melman Papers 5883: Frank McCulloch Papers
Weiss, Benjamin; Barbizon Corporation
7984593
- Cartoons: From the 1950's, in the ILGWU Justice by Bernard Seaman (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  booklet
- Zimmerman and Local 22 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  ff188 -- 7 photographs
- Strikes (Box 1, Folder 3)
  ff187 -- 4 photographs
- Homework - Lewis Hine (Box 1, Folder 4)
  ff186 -- 4 photographs
- D.D. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  ff185 -- 2 photographs
- Barbizon (Box 1, Folder 6)
  book
- Barbizon (Box 1, Folder 7)
  book - c.2
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 1, Folder 8)
  20 photographs
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 1, Folder 9)
  13 photographs
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 1, Folder 10)
  15 photographs
- News Clippings (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Contents of an unlabeled photo album (Box 1, Folder 12)
  27 photographs
- Barbizon photos (Box 2, Folder 1)
  17 photographs, news clippings
- Style Reference book by Barbizon: for Spring 1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Barbizon: Fall and Winter 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Barbizon: Fall and Winter 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Around the World with Barbizon (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Barbizon: Style Reference Book for Fall and Winter 1959 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Barbizon: Style Reference Book, Spring 1958 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Carefree Fabrics by Barbizon (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Barbizon: Spring/Summer 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- The Barbizon Corporation: Fiftieth Anniversary: Fall/Winter 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- News Clippings, Photographs, Contact Sheets (contents of a Photo Album) (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Oversize photo of inside of a clothing factory (Box 3, Folder 2)
  1 photograph
- Contents of a Photo Album (Box 3, Folder 3)
  kept together after dismantling the photo album -- 144 photographs, news clippings
- T.D.I. Gold Tournament (Box 4, Folder 1)
  2 Phonograph records - housed with collection (Artificial for sake of boxing) 6349 AV in box 1